啊太好了有灵魂伴侣
ah great well there's soulmate
没有五个人看起来很可爱
no five to company seem lovely
呃让我们带你四处看看
uh let's show you around
这是我们的接尿的桶
this is the bucket where our p freezes and
这就对了
that's it
你叫什么名字玻璃
what's your name glass
那是 moga 我又来了 你是
that's moga i'm again and you are
我一直在较低的牢房
i've been in a lower cells
比一个女人的影子
than a shadow with a female
我想我会喜欢它的忠告
think i'm gonna like it word of advice
holky 不喜欢被打扰
holky doesn't love to be disturbed
当她吃土豆的时候
while she's eating her potatoes kind of a
荧光笔每天为你闭嘴
highlighter per day shut up for you
肯定没有
sure thing haven't
你害羞 我没那么坏 一旦你了解我
you shy i'm not so bad once you get to know me
不要在那儿
don't be right there
我会不用手指来做这个然后弥补
i'm gonna do this without fingers and make it up
让我们试着留下深刻印象
let's try and impress
不是
not
幸运发现你的信仰神圣更接近
fortune found your faith divine come closer to be
只是党的
just of the party
樱桃游轮
cherry cruise
摇摇晃晃 让我们把挖掘机打走
and sway let's hit the digger away
停止那歌声
stop that singing
再见
goodbyes
赦免计数太难了
the absolution counts was too hard
不要把希望寄托在床上
Don't get your hopes up bed
你在说什么
what are you talking about
乔纳森这次坐在沙发上 他是个错误 cochra
Jonathan is on the couch for this time he's an error cochra
如果有人要和他在一起
if anyone's gonna freeze with him
不会发生
not gonna happen
告诉你坚持
tell you hold up
这是你的屁股他们砍我们
this is your ass they chopping us
领主联盟的授权
by authority of the lords alliance
这个赦免委员会现在将在
this absolution council will now come to order in the case of
Edgin Darvis 和 Holgar Kilber
Edgin Darvis and Holgar Kilber
这是因以下罪行被监禁的第二年
this is the second year of incarceration for the crimes of
品牌 larstony 和 skull dugrant
brand larstony and skull dugrant
本理事会的任务是确定
it is the task of this council to determine
你的活力部分是你说的话
your energibility for part what say you
贾斯勒夫人
lady jasler
Steam 理事会成员
steam members of the council
在我得到之前 我注意到乔纳森总理不是
before i get i noticed that Chancellor Jonathan is not
现在我们应该等一下
present should we perhaps wait
乔纳森议长被你可能开始的风暴耽搁了
Chancellor Jonathan was delayed by the storm you may begin
我懂了
i see
只是我们真的指望他死
it's just that we were really counting on him to his end
开始或挥动你的陈述
begin or wave your statement
自由意志
free will
我应该先给你一些背景信息
i should start by giving you some context
你可能会惊讶地发现我并不总是一个小偷
you may be surprised alert i wasn't always a thief
多年前我成为了竖琴派的一员
years ago i became a member of the harpers faction
宣誓与暴政作斗争的间谍网络
a network of spies who swear an oath to fight tyranny
捍卫被压迫者 不求回报
defend the oppressed and to ask nothing in return
我的妻子夏明明知道风险 但还是支持我的决定
my wife xia supported my decision even though she knew the risks
白天我需要雇佣兵
by day i need drop on mercenaries
音轨中的停止带
stop bands in the tracks
我们需要将成名的红衣巫师绳之以法
we need to bring fame red wizards to justice
晚上
by night
我回到我亲爱的妻子女儿基拉身边
i come home to my loving wife daughter Kira
老实说 当我开始质疑时它起作用了
to be honest it worked times when i began to question
不求回报属于自己的一部分
asking nothing in return part of my own
但我妻子总是说
but my wife would always say
你不必给我们一切
you Don't have to give us everything
你只需要给我们你所以什么是最新的黑暗
you only have to give us you so what's latest on dark
然后他在第二次等待时靠近你没听到什么
then he close by the second wait did you not hear what
他说对 要坚强 就是这样
he said right be strong it's just that
根据我对乔纳森的了解
based on what i know about Jonathan
我认为他特别容易接受我的故事
i think he be especially receptive to my story
我讨厌那是所有其他年份回到这里的方式
and i hate that's a way to all other year to come back in here
绝对是我们开始
absolutely here we go
当你是竖琴手时 你注定要树敌
when you're a harper you're bound to make enemies
有时那些敌人会来报复
and sometimes those enemies come looking for revenge
没有克拉伦斯可以修复红色巫师之刃造成的伤害
no Clarence can repair the damage from the red wizard's blade
没有办法让她复活
there was no way to revive her
当大海死去
when the sea died
为我自己的奉献服务
serving my devotion to my own
对不起 这只是
i'm sorry it's just
很难重温这个
hard to relive this
这里没有新闻业
without journalism here
我带着这个来
i came with this
但他错过了我背后故事中最重要的部分
but he missed the most important part of my back story
他怎么能评判我
how can he judge me
不知道我的动机
without knowing my my motivation
我们完全有能力在没有
we are entirely capable of deciding your case without
达纳森继续努力
darnathan get on with it
有时候我在哪里
sometimes where was i uh
晚上
by night
我回到我亲爱的妻子和你的艺术图拉的家
i come home to my loving wife and your art tura
你太过分了
you went back too far
停止拖延
stop stalling right
对不起 嗯 是的 粗略的
sorry um yeah broad strokes
接下来的几个月是
the next few months were
在我最倒角之中
among my most chamfer
这就是为什么我说霍尔加
that's why i meant holgar
她可怜我
she took pity on me
好吧 她可怜这个孩子
well she took pity on the baby
Holgar 是 rock bottom 的居民
holgar was a fellow resident of rock bottom
许多年前
many years before
她因为
she'd been cast out of her tribe for
爱上一个外面
falling in love with an outside
我们很快就变得像兄妹了
we quickly became like brother and sister
建立在信任和相互尊重基础上的关系
with a relationship built on trust and mutual respect
我们俩都没有钱 也没有诚实的赚钱方式
neither of us had money or an honest way to earn it
所以我们决定了一张诚实的桌子
so we decided a table honest and
我们尝试了一些新东西
we tried something new
Hamsubi Ala galactiriku safasakamathi ha
Hamsabiki Alagana Ginkam 生活条件集
Hamsabiki Alagana Ginkam on life condition set
舔 Kuchasa 帽子到 Hamsahiko eggjutkata
licking Kuchasa hat to Hamsahiko eggjutkata
是的 sukriyapa gitkamoka wow wahit
yes sukriyapa gitkamoka wow wahit
大奖是一些 bavana
jackpot is some bavana
milikaya 把一个乳白色的屁股
milikaya put a milky ass
嗯 我喜欢谁在前面
hum i like who's at the head
舔嗡嗡声 rbp 每个人和
licking hum rbp everybody and
当你意识到分开的东西时就会中毒
toxicated when you realize that what separates
一直想要的可以细如痛
always wanted can be as thin as a pain
你可能想知道
you may be wondering
如何
how
我们可以和一个年轻女孩继续这种犯罪生活方式
we can carry on this criminal lifestyle with a young girl at
家
home
我们不记得了
well we didn't remember
我们还在西蒙增加了一座新兵大楼
there was a building of recruit we also added in Simon
所以 so so swasher 骗子排在第四
so so swasher con man in fourth
我们成为了一个团队
we became a team
是的更多主题但是
yes more themes but
我试着把它放在某个扫描仪上我们从来没有伤害过任何人
i tried to hold this to a certain scanner we never harmed anyone
我们只会从那些认为它相信的人那里抢劫
and we only rob from those who feel it believes
但是当我们遇到巫师索菲娜时一切都变了
but everything changed when we met the wizard Sofina
我们对她几乎一无所知
we knew almost nothing about her
只是她需要我们的帮助
only that she wanted our help
抢劫玉米的要塞
robbing corn's keep
那是一场艰苦的斗争
that's a harper struggle
我不知道你是否听说过 我敢肯定
i Don't know if you've heard of it i'm sure
乔纳森麻烦
Jonathan hassle
无价之宝从
the priceless relaxes from the
只有在巴普斯才能进入螺栓的门
doors that only in barpers can gain access to the bolt
这就是苏菲娜来找我们的原因
which is why suffina came to us
起初我拒绝了我不会弯腰那么低
at first i refused i wouldn't stoop that low
但后来 Forge 告诉我 在遗迹和号角中保留着
but then forge told me that among the relics and horns keep
有一个
there was a
觉醒石碑
tablet of re awakening
能够让一个死去的人复活
capable of bringing back a single deceased person
即使被红巫师之刃杀死
even when killed by a red wizards blade
你可能会看到这是怎么回事
you can probably see where this is going
为什么我不能来
why can't i come
抱歉治愈这个太危险了
sorry cure this one is too dangerous
那你不应该去
then you shouldn't go
我们有我们需要的一切
we have everything that we need
哦 是的 看这是最后一个
oh yeah look this is the last one
相信我
trust me
你知道吗
you know what
你马上回来
you right back
我没有告诉她毛巾的事
i didn't tell her about the towel to
如果一切都消失了 让她心碎
break her heart if it all went to shed and
呃摆脱它去了
uh to shed it went
她得到了时光荏苒的父母钻石
she's got the times gone parents diamonds
加倍并保持安全
double and keep care of safe
你有我的工作
you have my work
判我再判两年或 20 年的房子的话
house words who sentence me to another two years or 20
就此而言
for that matter it
永远不会受到足够的惩罚
would never be punishment enough for the
我犯下的最严重的罪行
worst crime i ever committed
抢夺我女儿的父亲
robbing my daughter of her father
但要知道如果你真的选择释放我
but know that if you do choose to free me
用我余下的时间努力写错
spend the rest of my days trying to write that wrong
任何你想要的
anything you want that
我很好
i'm good
在你宣布你的决定之前 我恳求你取悦
before you announce your decision i implore you to please
等着你
wait for you
我不能告诉你我必须走开
i can't tell you i'll have to step away
她在画土豆
she's drawing potatoes
还在呼吸
still breathing
哈哈哈哈
hahahaha
空了一会儿
empty for a while
你认为 Forge 把她带到哪里去了
where do you think forge took her
我不能在像城市一样画画的短教练中出现
i can't seem in a short coach who draws like cities
一些晚餐你和你的妻子
some suppa you and your wife
喜欢
like
与那个
be with that
那些嘴唇在微风中生长
those lips grows just the breeze
所以我们对鲍德之门进行投票
so we take a vote down to balder's gate
然后往北走
and then head north
好吧 我们正在寻找草料 我们会在拜访时付钱给马洛
well we're looking for forage we'll pay marlow in a visit
你确定你真的想让自己经历那什么
you sure do you really want to put yourself through that what
如果他不想和你说话
if he doesn't want to talk to you
这与他想要什么无关 而与关闭有关
it's not about what he wants it's about closure
他说
he say
他会让她说他不再是你的丈夫了
he will let her say he wasn't your husband anymore was that
关闭
closure
你不会明白我不
you wouldn't understand i Don't
我清楚地清楚地不
i clearly clearly Don't
就是它
is that
王八蛋
son of a bitch
Forge is lord 永远不会过冬
forge is lord never winter
那个小丑是怎么做到的
how did that clown pull that off
只要他得到治愈 我不在乎拜托
as long as he's got cure i don't care come on
我们走吧
let's go
谢谢妈妈我的嘴唇
thanks mom my lips
它们对你的脸来说太大了
they're too big for your face what
很多人喜欢我的嘴唇
a lot of people like my lips
从未见过这个肮脏的地方
never seen this place of grotter
一定要参加烈日运动会
must be coming into the high sun games
哦 在他们被取缔之前 我爸爸带我去了最后一个
oh my dad took me to last one before they were outlawed
有人去过
anyone went
出色地
well
与你的怪物最后一轮的一致意义
one consistent meaning to the final round with your monster
和榜样
and example guys so
很高兴看到我们是否刚刚迷失了这座城市
it's nice to see if we're just lost the city
多久了
how long has it been
两年
two years
不 我们在这里等了多久
no how long have we been waiting here
爸爸
dad
你好
welcome
库拉
cura
我很想你 因为一个小虫子
i missed you so much for a little bug
我每天都在想你
i thought about you every day
完全是这个
completely this
这些是什么
what are they
男士哦
men's oh
谢谢
thanks
你还好吗
have you been okay
Forge叔叔对我很好
uncle forge has been very good to me
叔叔
uncle
饲料
forage
唔
hmm
想见你
wants to see you
仍然戴上你给我的那支笔
still wear the pen you got me like that
我有时用它在城堡周围停留
i use it to stick around the castle sometimes
觉得你在这里真奇怪
so strange think you're here
治疗看
cure look
我想让你知道我很抱歉
i want you to know i am so sorry
对于事情的结果我冒了风险
for how things turned out i took a risk
我没有还清
i didn't pay off
你为什么对我生气
why do you look mad at me
因为你表现得好像这不是你的错
cause you're acting like it wasn't your fault
他们在那里
there they are
哈哈
ha ha
哦 线程多么美妙的惊喜来了
oh thread what a wonderful surprise come
我有没有发现一点灰色
do i spy a little bit of gray
我确实喜欢它 它很糟糕 但你看起来像个教授
i do i like it it's scoundrely but professorial you look like a
你知道你长得像吗
do you know right you look like
一个有秘密的红色渔夫
a well red fisherman with secrets
哈哈哈
hahaha
对数
logar
他的最后一年
his last year
但我告诉你我认为你会服役更长时间
but i tell you what i did think you'd serve longer
哦
oh
是的
yeah
我们得到了
we we gotten
真的发布了
really released
良好的行为是的
good behavior yeah
宝贝宝贝好啊我明白了
baby baby good ah i see
好你好
well welcome
你好回来
welcome back
好吧 这是令人毛骨悚然的
well that's bristering
又热又热
bristeringly hot and yet again
卡罗尔 我们真的应该和厨房工作人员谈谈
Carol we really should speak to the kitchen staff
因为很明显没必要这么热
because there's a clear no need for it to be this hot
是的是的是的 所以你是贝弗冬天的领主吗？
yeah yeah the the t side so how are you the lord of bever winter
就在你入狱之前
right before you went off to prison
你向我收取了装备费用
you charged me with gear as well being
当时没想太多
didn't think much of it at the time
但有一刻我看着她的眼睛
but there came a moment when i looked into her eyes
我突然知道我必须成为一个更好的人
and i suddenly knew i had to be a better man
显然我不能用石头把宝物还回去
obviously i couldn't give back the treasures with stone
所以当大人永远不会失败时 我会抓住机会尝试
so when lord never Ember fail ill i'll seize the chance to try
并有所作为
and make a difference
警卫的钱远离我的竞选活动
and the money from guards keep paved away from my campaign
但我会告诉你这个
but i will tell you this
一个人做不到
couldn't have done it alone
她在那里
and there she is
你记得萨芬娜
you remember safina
你还在和她一起工作是她让我们被抓住了
you're still working with her she's the one that got us caught
不是真的 没有我们所有人
not true no without how we all
会被抓住的
would have been caught
从那以后她就成了
since then she has become
我的最高顾问
my top advisor
茶是灼热的我做
the tea is scorching i do
抱歉天气太热了
apologize it's scorching hot
嗯
um
索菲亚
Sophia
你介意那么多吗
would you mind that much
突然
suddenly
很好 谢谢你
good thank you i that
我没想到你会把手指伸进去
i didn't realize you were gonna put your finger in
在地毯上
in the carpet
我以后需要那个
i'm gonna need that for later well
如果你能给我们治疗药片 否则我就在路上
if you'll give us the tablet cure or i will be on our way
当然这就是你回来的原因
of course that's why you came back
不 它不是给我用的那块富有的财富
no it wasn't for me used for that tablet of riches riches
不 它是一种唤醒药片 对不起 这是什么
no it's the it's a tablet of reawakening i'm sorry what's this
现在
now
之所以
the reason why
我同意最高的是
i agreed to the to the highest is that
这是他告诉你的吗
is that what he's told you
我离开你是为了更多的财富
that i left you for more riches
我告诉她真相她很清楚
i told her the truth she has a bright to know it
他一直在骗你 我
he's been lying to you here i
我想
i wanted to
我想带你妈妈回来哦
i wanted to bring your mother back oh
快来看看我
and come on look i
我知道你们多么渴望得到宽恕 但我向你们保证
i know how much you crave for forgiveness but i promise you all
眼睛不是你蛇的样子
eyes is not the way you snake
你他妈的很清楚他想要什么你为什么不告诉我
you know damn well what he was after why why didn't you tell me
如果你是为妈妈做的
if you were doing it for mom
因为如果我失败了 我不想让你再次失去她
because i didn't want you to lose her again if i failed
但你不能责怪那个可怜的女孩不信任你
but you can't blame the poor girl for distrusting you
毕竟
after all
自从你踏进房间以来你就一直在撒谎我是新来的
you have been lying since you're set foot in the room i'm new
你逃脱了我们正试图回到你身边解决错误
you escaped we were trying to get back to you bug cure
看着我看着我
look at me look at me
我向你发誓那是一块重新觉醒的石板
i swear to you it was a tablet of re awakening
我是为妈妈为我们所有人做的 你必须相信我
i was doing it for mom for all of us you have to trust me
当你离开我时他告诉我要相信你
he told me to trust you when you left me
Kira no wait wait Kira 给个时间给个时间
Kira no wait wait Kira give a time give a time
她因为你的缺席而怨恨你多年
she's had years to resent you for your absence
你已经用了很多年毒害她来对付我 不
you've had years to poison her against me no
那不是真的
that is not true
我们很少谈到做
we very rarely spoke of doing
给他他为平板电脑而来的东西
give him what he came for the tablet
我不认为我会退货
i don't think i will be returning it
或者
or
你的躯干给那个主人
your torso for that master
混蛋
bastard
现在你在地板上哦 我讨厌看到那个
and now you're in the floor oh i hate to see that
萨维娜真的是一个非常非常强大的巫师
Savina really is a very very powerful wizard
你会有
you'd have
以为你会在最后一次了解到
thought that you'd have learned that at the last time
她困住了你
she trapped you
你一直想让我们得到上帝不
you always wanted us to get god no
我想了
i wanted
你急于被煮熟但他设法逃脱了一些东西
you anxiety to get cooked but he managed to escape something
这些年来一起为这个女巫做了一个新的双十字架
all these years together a new double crosses for this witch
永远不要相信为此而说的命令
never put your trust in a command say for this
基拉真的很开心
Kira really is happy and
很好地照顾你 我真的
very well taken care of you and i have truly
把别人当作自己的
come to another as my own
我实际上从来没有
i i never actually
看到成为父亲的样子 直到我成为一个父亲
saw the appear of being a father till i became one
但
but
拥有另一个人
to have another person
仰望你 让你按照自己的形象塑造他们
look up to you and allow you to to shape them in your own image
有点像神
it's a bit like a god
好吧 我是一个
well i'm a
我是上帝和领主 我真的做得很好 black wood
i'm a god and the lord i am really doing all right black wood
你能回到监狱吗
could you possibly return to prison
并且短到内裤
and and be short to panty
出色地
well
我必须离开我是
i must away i am
从最古老的门和水里期待两个最富有的人
expecting two of the wealthiest men from oldest gate and water
深谈回归的高沙游戏
deep to talk about the high sand games which are back
哈哈
haha
所以有些东西不是吗
so there's something isn't it
看到你更好真的很高兴
it was genuinely lovely to see you better
你得好好把她弄出去
you gotta get her out of there well
我们现在需要考虑自己的高度
we need to think about our own heights right now
你没看错
you got this right
我知道你没有跪下
i know you don't on your knees
帅玩
handsome play
是锤子公会房间的作品吗
is that the work of guild room for hammer
你怎么知道
how'd you know
主要在一半
mainly on a half
等得怎么样
how's the wait does it perry
天还是黑的
it's dark still
非常好 现在请低下头
very nice now put your heads down
等待
wait
你用什么清洁它
what do you clean it with
你快要失去理智了
you're about to lose your head
这就是你所关心的
this is what you're concerned
如果你不介意的话
if you wouldn't mind
煮火石
boiled Flint
籽油
seed oil
一次应该是一周一次
once a moment should be once a week
这就是为什么你要在中间休息
that's why you getting rest on the mid
好吧 把它砍掉
okay chop it off
砍掉它让我们开始吧
chop it off let's do it
哦 我们现在拿到了
oh we got them now
在我们离开这座城市之前
before we leave the city well
今年
this year
不不不
no not
我想确定你是其中之一
i wanted to make sure you were one
我知道我会看看我们是否可以想知道
i knew i'd see if we could wonder
我仍然认为它可能会有所不同
i still think it might be different
你必须明白吗
will you have to understand
当他失去你母亲时
when he lost your mother
谁会迷失自我
who would have lost himself
他为什么要谎报第一名
why did he lie about the top one
也许他羞于承认这么久以来他放弃了多少
maybe he was ashamed to admit how much he'd given up for so long
我应该进去
i should probably go sweet in
好吧 他走了 他走了
well he's gone idea he's gone
我给了他平板电脑扳手
i gave him the tablet wrenches
他离开了
he left
能做什么
what could do
对不起
i'm sorry
我想让你知道即使他不是
and i want you to know even if he isn't therefore
我一直想要
i always want
我知道
i know
事实上你看到了我的优点
the fact that you see good in me
让我相信可能只是一些东西
makes me believe that there might just be something
我们可以向她的房间射一支带有信息的箭
we could shoot an arrow with a message into her room
如果它回答怎么办
what if it answer
这是我们必须承担的风险
that's a risk we're gonna have to take
用箭杀死了我的女儿 不 不是
killing my daughter with an arrow no it's not
即使她收到消息她真的来了她想到的
even if she got the message she really come she thinks of
伪造或爸爸
forge or dad
你原谅那座城堡并推倒我们自己
you forgive that Castle and take down ourselves
那太疯狂了是的
that's crazy yeah
城堡永远不会比玉米更紧让你知道
Castle never is tighter than corn's keeping you know
那是怎么回事
what happened with that
我们真的需要一个团队
we really need a team
会帮助我们的团队 我们没有什么可以付给他们的
team who's gonna help us out we have nothing to pay them with
伪造确实
forge does
他说最富有的
he said the richest
人们前来为烈日游戏下注
people were coming to bet on the high sun games
在那发财哦
be a fortune in that oh
是的
yeah
更不用说平板电脑了
not to mention the tablet
治愈会消失
the cure will go
我们出于正当理由抛弃了她
we abandon her for the right reason
我知道我不会那样说
i know i wouldn't put it like that
但是啊是啊
but uh yeah yeah
我们为这个团队得到了什么
what do we get for this team
你知道我想知道 Simon 是否还在 triborn
you know i wonder if Simon's still in triborn
西蒙是个糟糕的帽子来源
Simon's a terrible source of hat
看来两年后我相信他会变得更好
it seemed in two years i'm sure he's got the better
没有人能对这一把戏望尘莫及
no one can hold a candle to this trick
这个怎么样
how about this one
人们喜欢新割草的气味
people like the smell of fresh cut grass
闻到它被刷成十字架
smell that it's brushed a cross
为什么五岁
why five year old
可以神奇地做到这一点
can do that magically
但你能做到这一点吗
but can you do this absolutely
他没有好转
he hasn't gotten better
我不认为这是关于他在那里做什么
i don't think it's about what he's doing up there
这很难像这样有点模糊
this is quite hard to be slightly blurry like this
非常模糊但稍微模糊
to be very blurry but to be slightly blurry
这才是真正的魔法
that's the real magic
他在编一些书
he's making up in some books
少它只是东西
less it's only things
他在撒谎 这全是流行游艇 搞定他
it's all pop yacht he's lying get him
我不喜欢这个节目
i'm not loving the show
签名哦上帝留下来尴尬你会没事的
sign oh god staying for an awkward you'll be okay
我本可以想要你的力量来刺
i could have wanted your force to the prick
一旦我们离开那个错误
as soon as we left that fault
所以彼得想杀了我只是袖手旁观
so Peter tried to kill me just stood by
你知道这个谣言
you know this rumor
她让上帝永远不会跌倒
she made lord never have a fall
生病与董事会扫清道路
ill to clear the way with the board
魔法在一个我不知道的洞里
magic is on a hole i Don't know
我卖空了自己 我很抱歉你的表演
i'm selling yourself short i'm sorry your show
是的 你可以用刚割过的草来打她
yeah you can hit her with that fresh cut grass trip
是的 看起来很有趣
yeah it's funny look
我不怪你想救基拉
i Don't blame you for wanting to save Kira
我喜欢敲前办公室鲈鱼的想法
and i love the idea of knocking forward office perch
但
but
抢劫卡森永远不会消除抢劫观众的风险
robbing Carson never isn't wipe the risk robbing your audiences
你绝望了吗
a broke are you desperately
我本来打算今晚睡在剧院里 但现在
i was planning on sleeping in the theater tonight but now
这似乎是轻率的
that seems imprudent
所以我们甚至知道什么样的街机
so do we even know what sort of arcade
魔法正在保护这本书
magic is protecting the book
我们会查明你是怎么偷偷过去的
we're gonna find out how you gonna sneak past
整座城堡都看着我
the entire castle watch me
没有画它可能是一个狂野的形状
no drew it may be a wild shape
他们进出并将其检测为
they get in and out and detect it as a
有老鼠或鹿
there's a mouse or a deer
是的 一只鹿很好地融合了城堡里的所有其他鹿
yes a deer well blended all the other deer in the castle
不要标记我
don't mark me
我找到一个德鲁伊
i find a druid
我认识一个德鲁伊多立克 她真的是独一无二的
i know a druid doric she's truly one of a kind
在剧院听起来很浪漫
sounds romantic in theater
是啊什么
yeah what
然而 看到我发现我缺乏自尊没有吸引力
see however found my lack of self esteem unattractive
不是你最好的交易
not your best trade
谢谢
thank you
以威廉王子堡的名义
in the name of fort prince William
囚犯在这里已经死了
the prisoner is here by senses to death
我的烦恼
my dispeplement
说我们领导人坏话的罪名
for the crime of speaking ill of our leader
粘土上的翡翠永远不会让
the emerald on clay will never let
正义不能因为我的麻烦而被扼杀
justice cannot be killed on my trouble
门在这儿
the door's been over here
这是一个
that's a
做很多愚蠢的事情
be a lot of foolish something
很乱
it's messing
在这里 你在等
here here you are wait wait
是我
it's me
西蒙
Simon
西门谁
Simon who
哎哟西蒙
ouch Simon
霍玛巫师
homa sorcerer
我叫做什么
i call what to do
他说我让你难过不是因为我做的任何事
he said i made you feel sad not for anything i did just
我是谁
from who i was
哦
oh
是啊是啊
yeah yeah
你在这里做什么
what are you doing here
我们需要一只鹿
we need a deer
我们不需要鹿
we don't need a deer
我们要记下幸运的时候
we're gonna take down fortunates when
所以我不得不来一杯酒
so i had to come a liquor
我出生于人类决定他们不想要一个爱逗乐的孩子
i was born to humans decided they didn't want a teafling child
另一个带我进去
the one else took me in
享受绣花飞地以保护他们
enjoying the embroide enclave to protect them well
明白这就是你加入我们的全部原因
see that's all the reason you join us
我们是唯一一个看不见城堡的人
we're the only one who get that castle unseen
告诉我们正在做什么
tells what we're doing with
正如你想象的那样 我不相信人类 我发现你是
as you can imagine i don't trust humans i find you to be
仇恨和自私
hateful and selfish
你不会 我是
you won't i'm
发现你是个小男人 如果它有帮助的话 我只是个性感的人
finding you to be a little man if it helps i'm only hot human
但你是个坏巫师不西蒙
but you're a bad sorcerer no Simon
他是个强大的巫师
he's a mighty sorcerer
他是 o'more 元素的后代
he's a descendant of elements for o'more
成功的唯一方法是
the only way to succeed in this is that
相信它可以做到
confidence that it can be done
他没有
he doesn't yeah
我想那更好
i suppose that's better
看 西蒙可能没有我的智慧
look Simon may not have my wit
或抱直你
or hold you straight
但当它指望这只年轻的手美味时
but when it counts this young hand delicious
这就是为什么约瑟夫
it's why Joseph
他也是你认识的唯一 Socier
he's also the only Socier you know
或者你没有帮助
or you're not helpful
正是你带来的
is it exactly that you bring through this
我是一个你知道的我是一个计划者
me i'm a i'm a planner you know
我制定计划
i make plans
你已经制定了计划那么你现在有什么山谷
you've already made the plan so what valley do you have now
如果计划失败 我会制定新计划
if the plan fails existing plan i'd make a new plan
所以你制定了失败的计划
so you make plans that fail no
他还玩循环霍根不相关相信我
he also plays the loop hogan not relevant trust me
我是不可或缺的
i'm indispensable
出色地
well
我们试图取消锻造工作的计划都没有
none of the plans we've tried to take down forge of work
我们敢于质疑我们是如何上台的
we dare to question how we came to power
所以他宣布我们为敌
so he declared us enemies
开始摧毁我们的家园
began destroying our homes
处决我们的人
and executing our people
如果你不尽快为我们停下来
if you don't stop for us soon
将没有什么可捍卫的
there'll be nothing left to defend
这样做不是为了钱
not doing this for the money
为说话到最后的人做这件事
do this for the people who talk to the end
当没有人会
when no one else would
所以我们会保留你的份额
so we'll keep your share then
供热
supply the heat
想象他们
imagine them
姐姐
sister
但你一直遇到我最依赖的弟子
but you have always met the disciple i rely on most
你的冷静
of your calm
意思是你是我的印记
meaning that you're sigils from me
我宁愿做朋友而不是因为我花时间
i'd rather be friends to unfait i'm spending on the hour
带着食物
with food
那是可以忍受的
that has been sufferable
但如果没有他 我们永远不会走到这一步
but we never would have come this far without his
工作
job
活着的人已经跟随这个世界够久了
the living has been followed this world long enough
太烦人了 但你这里的工作快完成了
takes so much annoying but your work here is nearly complete
脱下你的兜帽我注意到
with your hood off i noticed
可能最好保留那个你知道你在博览会上读过的旧东西
probably best to keep that old you know you read with the fair
不像你应该在外面那么受你好
not as popular as you should be outside
在那里 当然你即将成为相当大的是
there and of course you're about to be considerably yes
受你好的
popular
但是离我很远 永远不会告诉你该怎么做
but but far far beard from me never to tell you what to do
cordwell 和 pedrodust 到了 我要给
and cordwell and pedrodust arrived i was gonna give
哦 听着 我真的必须对这些椅子做点什么
oh for listen i really have to do something about these chairs
现在我想你会发现我们已经采取了
now i think you will find that we have taken
保护资产的所有可能措施
every imaginable measure to protect the asset that you may
或者在烈日游戏期间可能不会选择投注
or may not choose the wager during the high sun games
我们在每个窗户城堡上都有纽波特颜色
we have Newport colour sits on every window castle
如果警报响起 则无人进入或
if the alarm is raised nobody gets in or
出去
out
然后
then
有
there is
替代本身
the alt itself
我的成就顾问雅典娜可以给你所有的折扣
my achieve advisors Athena can give you all the discounts
它受到 Morden Kanan 奥术封印的保护
it is protected by the Arcane seal of Morden Kanan
出色地
well
也许不是所有的细节 但
perhaps not all the details but
足以说这是一个非常强大的法术
suffice to say it is a seriously powerful spell
我可以问一下是什么促使你恢复比赛吗
might i inquire what prompted you to resume the games
主从不琥珀色
lord never amber
认为他们很残忍
considered them quite brutal
上帝从来没有琥珀 我是非常不同的人 例如
lord never amber and i are very different men for example
我更喜欢起来走动 他更喜欢植物人
i prefer to be up and about he prefers to be in a vegetative
哈哈哈
hahaha
你太可怕了
you are terrible
哈哈哈
hahaha
我可以不是你知道我
i can be not you know i
事实是游戏
the truth is that the games
将城市凝聚在一起
bring the city together like nothing else
这不是政府的角色
and it is not the role of government
拒绝人们所渴望的
to deny the people what they crave
或者
or
剥夺你们这些有钱的混蛋从中获利的权利
to deny you rich bastards the right to profit of them
哈哈哈
hahaha
现在谁想要茶点
now who wants refreshments
一个狂野的形状是莫里斯
a wild shape is a Morris
所以她确实成为了亲爱的
so she did become a dear
我想起了她的手 你真的确定 salfina 看到了吗
i think of her hand are you absolutely sure about salfina saw
她的市场我不知道我不能指望自己
her markets i wonder i couldn't count on to himself
老四一直都知道他把我女儿弄进去了
fourth knew all along he's got my daughter in there
和一个红色巫师
with a red wizard
故障由一种叫做莫蒂的东西保护
fault is protected by something called Morty
开曼街机海豹
Cayman's arcade seal
不仅仅是迦南是的
more than canaan yeah
这是一个
that's a
哦可惜但是
oh pity but
如果一个金库还有更多的迦南
if a vault has more than canaans still
我们不会进入它是坚不可摧的 你不能
we're not getting in it's impenetrable can't you just
用魔法打开它
open it with magic
埃里克
Eric
每个人都认为你可以用魔法解决任何问题
how everyone thinks that you can solve any problem with magic
有限制 这不是一些
there are limits this isn't some
睡前故事这是真实的世界
bedtime story this is the real world
所以没有办法打开它
so there's no way to open it
不要说我是世界上最强大的巫师之一
Don't mean if i were one of the world's most powerful sorcerers
所以不 或者如果我们有分离的家
so no or if we had the home of disjunction
它是一种头盔 可以禁用所有近乎不同的图表
the way it's a helmet that disables all near vary chartments
但没关系这东西失踪了很久
but it doesn't matter the thing went missing ages
我们完成了
and we're done
啊来吧
ah come on
我们能解决什么问题
what's the problem we can
找到那张专辑
find that album
即使我们这样做了 我也可以在不调整它的情况下使用它
even if we did i can use it without a tuning to it
我很糟糕
which i'm terrible
如果你能做到
if you can do it
我知道你能不能说这不是第三次 yeah
i know you can you saying that doesn't be a third yeah
但你说我不能 但你不能 我不会
but you say it does i can't but you can't i won't
就说不啊
just say no ah
好吧 我们能不能把它放在地面的声音之间
fine can we just keep this between that sound of the ground
什么士气
what morale
胡尔卡知道你的头盔在哪里
Hulka knows where the helmet is you
我的部落在埃文战争中为它与龙的崇拜战斗
my tribe fought the cult of the Dragon over it at the Evan Wars
我们可以问问他们会在哪里
we could just ask them where it would
那场战斗是一个世纪前他们都死了
that battle was a century ago they're all dead
所以用魔法问他
so ask him with magic
他只是做了一个完整的演讲 他无法解决问题
he just made a whole speech how he can't fix
一切都充满魔力
everything with magic
其实那不是
actually that isn't
你可以让死者复活
you can bring back the dead
我不能带回来
i can't bring the back
但我有这个令牌可以让我问尸体和问题
but i have this token that lets me ask corpses and questions
然后他们回去死了
and then they go back to be dead
是的 这太棒了
yeah it's fairly wonderful
这真是太棒了
it's fairly wonderful
结束永远的战争谢谢你儿子的钻井平台
off the ever wars thank you son for the rigs
啊什么
oh what
只需用魔法支付
just pay it with magic
是的
yeah
我们在哪里
of where we are
你为什么要这样对自己
why would you do that to yourself
我只是去拿一些我的东西
i'm just gonna pick up some of my things
你画了百叶窗
you painted the shutters
男鹿
oga
你好 Marlemon
hello Marlemon
那是Marlemon哦
that's Marlemon oh
是的
yeah
我们第一次见到他时你有点惊讶
you're a little surprise the first time we met him
我以为你的刑期更长
i thought your sentence was longer
我从那里逃了出来
i busted out of there
拯救老奥加
save old oga
所以你最近在做什么
so what have you been up to
嗯 平常有我的花园
huh the usual got my garden
在写我的书
working on my book
我看你还有我给你的那根手杖
i see you still have that walking stick i gave you
是的
yeah
好吧
yeah well
如果你愿意 你可以带走它
you can you can take it with you if you want
格温不喜欢漫无边际
Gwen's not much for rambling
格温 你在这里很性感
Gwen you're hot darling in here
当然 一群山谷人在这里工作哦 你好
of course a pack of valley working out of here oh hello
这是谁
who's this
那么哦格温这是
then oh Gwen this is
弹簧哦
Pogo oh
很多关于你
a lot about you
我会摇晃你但是呃
i'll shake you around but uh
乐趣
pleasure
一把有多长
how long is handful
我是
i'm
只是路过 会和 nesmay 以南的一些尸体交谈
just passing through gonna talk to some corpses south of nesmay
哦
oh
伟大的
great
要去吃晚饭了
gonna get washed up a supper
我们有什么
what we have in
我治愈了一只鹅 我收集了一些泡菜嗯
i cured a goose and i gathered some pickleberries hmm
漂亮的躁狂症
nice mania hoka
所以你们两个在这里待了多久
so how long have you two going on here
她让你开心了吗
did she make you happy
比我快乐
happier than i did
好吧 我会这样说 她让她诚实地生活 她
well i'll put it this way she makes her living honestly she
不喝自己傻
doesn't drink herself silly
她不会让我哭泣
and she doesn't make me weep
在凌晨想知道她在哪里
in the small hours wonder where she is
我很痛苦
i was in pain
我被放逐是因为我该死的部落和你在一起
i was banished for my damn tribe to be with you
我试图为我们建造一个家 这样你就可以忘记它
and i tried to build us a home so you could forget that
但你永远做不到
but you never could
格温看起来很可爱
Gwen seems lovely
你应得的
you deserve that
谢谢
thank you
你知道当你离开时我失去了我的家人
you know when you left i lost my family
我很幸运找到了另一个
i've been fortunate enough to find another
我希望你能做到这一点
and i wish nothing less than that for you
一个甜蜜的老没有希望
a sweet old no hope
我们要收拾草料
we're gonna take down forage
我要展示 marliman 和他们的尝试
i'm gonna show marliman and the out trying they
让我走是愚蠢的
were fools to let me go
一笔财富
a fortune
誓言或假神圣接近
vow or fake divine come close
喝葡萄汁
to tobing the juice of the vine
我的许多族人在这里为战斗献出了生命
so many of my kind gave their lives a battle here
我一直想象我会像这样被埋葬在圣地
i'd always imagined i'd be burying in sacred ground like this
是的
yeah
我们有一把铲子
we got a shovel
好的
okay
西蒙有这个
Simon has this one
我读到他的神职人员令牌上的意图应该在这里
i read the intentation on his clerics token should be here
某处是的
somewhere yeah
好吧 一旦死人复活
all right once the dead man is revives
我们一直在问五个问题
we've been asking five questions at which point
他会再次死去
he would die again
永不复活五个五个问题
never to be re revived five five questions
我不知道这就是它的工作原理它看起来很武断
i didn't know that's just how it works it seems arbitrary
你知道
you know
车辙这个
rut this
愉快
delightful
也许我不是说
maybe i'm not saying
谁害怕米妮·斯塔森
who was it scared of Minnie starson
开始了
here we go
你在谈论机场吗 是的 太好了
were you killing about the airport yes great
我是说
i mean
我不适合你
i'm not for you
我很抱歉你丢失了以前的问题
i'm sorry for your lost former question right
是的 不 不 我不是为了你 把那算作一个问题 是的
yes no no i'm not for you did that count as a question yes
该死的
dammit
只有在我说好的时候才回答
only answer when i talked okay
是的 你为什么最后说好
yes why did you say okay at the end of that
我没有叫
i didn't hoot
太棒了 铲子在哪里
fantastic where's the shovel
所以卡尔加
so karga
在战斗中你看到毁灭头盔了吗
during the battle did you see the helmet of destruction
它拥有
it was in possession
哦 我的长官
oh my chief
标准的灰狼好吧好
standard grim Wolf okay good
以及 stanhard grim Wolf 对它做了什么
and what did stanhard grim Wolf do with it
逆龙破行
moving against the dragon break
把它抱在怀里让我免于崩溃和所有成本
take this to the embrace keep me from breakdown and all costs
和世界的季节
and the season of the world
那是我记得的最后一件事
that's the last thing i remember
哦耶
oh yeah
谢谢你的帮助
thanks for your helpful
让我们直接去找标准的广告牌
let's go look for standard billboard straight hang on hang on
你为什么不让他放弃他们的问题
why aren't you gonna ask him to lose their questions
问他
ask him
你对冲浪的控制是什么 他很清楚
what you're in control of the surf thing he knows well
你不能就这样离开他 看看杆子
you can't just leave him like that look at the pole bloke
哦很好
oh fine
你最喜欢的食物是什么
what's your favorite food
哎哟没有聚会它不安静
ouch no party it's not quiet
你喜欢猫不太好
you like cats not really okay
什么是太加上我不好吗
what's too plus do i'm bad
数学
a math
你感觉好点了吗 不
do you feel better no
通常最有主见的决定只是继续
oftentimes the most ownerest decision only to continue
是时候撤退
is when to retreat
我承担订单
i assume the order
我不能在我的背后摇滚来传递疾病十字架
i cannot in my back rock to deliver the illness cross
如果你描述
if you describe
menu salifi 刚刚越过山脊
menu salifi just make it over the ridge
有一点战斗
there was a little bit of the battle
当我从嘴里滑落时 我的场地在开始时就滑落了
as i slipped off my mouth my court slipped on the start
然后你参加了战斗不
and then you went into the battle no
我死了
i died
来自傻瓜
from the fool
但是 stanard grimos city 把头盔给了然后 salified
but stanard grimos city gave the helmet to then salified
那是你不是吗
that's you isn't it
我是 Sven salified 那么兄弟
i'm Sven salified then's what brother
这是一场噩梦
this is a nightmare
因为你好罗伊
cause hello Roy
我受了伤 失去了我的马
i was wounded and had lost my horse
当我逃离战场
as i escaped the field of battle
我不关心我自己
i didn't care about myself
我只需要保证头盔安全
i just needed to keep the helmets safe
这是一件打扰 zas Tam 标记的事情
it was a thing who bother mark of zas Tam
我等待致命一击
i waited for the killing blow
但它从来没有来过
but it never came
他有一个好办法
he had a kind way
他告诉我他叫臧延丹
he told me his name was Zang Yendan
他逃离了 Zas Tam 现在还活着
he had fled Zas Tam and now lived
我死后流亡
in exile as i died
他答应保证头盔安全
he promised to keep the helmet safe
出于某种原因我相信他
and for some reason i believed him
你在开玩笑吧
you're joking
一个善良的家庭 我说实话
a kind fam i speak truth
你说崇拜那个粉丝撒谎 你白白死了
you speak worship that fan lied and you died for nothing
死胡同的头盔
the helmets of dead end
而我必须找到通往世界的另一条路
while i have to find another way to the world
不 我听说过 Zenk
no i've heard of Zenk
他是圣骑士
he's a paladin
他帮助飞地击败了塔利斯的牧师
he helped the enclave to beat the clerics of Talis
我也知道这个名字
i know the name as well
我叔叔说 Zenk 挡住了一个旁观者
my uncle said Zenk fended off a beholder
只用一个购物金
using only a shopping gold
一把锋利的葫芦
a sharp and gourd
东西店
something shop
粉丝是谋杀故事的结尾
the fans are murders end of story
什么
what
我也听说过他
i've heard of him too
不
no
他和我堂兄吵架了 neonorok 说他是个好人
he fought with my cousin and neonorok says he's a good man well
你们都可以去找到这个可爱的
you could all go find this lovely
zank 和编织彼此的头发我会找到另一种方式
zank and braid each other's hair i'll find another way
他有什么问题
what's his problem
他在粉丝中享有盛誉
he's got history with the fans
我知道你的感受
i know how you're feeling
但我们没时间了
but we're running out of time
我打败了你
i beat the trains of you
现在你不会这样做是为了拯救她和关心她
now you wouldn't you'd be doing it to save her and care
但如果 zank 结果是个混蛋
but if zank turns out to be a prick
我会把他们分开
i'll split them right down the mill
尤其
especially
我们会失去什么
what have we got to lose
任何人都知道愚蠢的 zenk 在哪里
anyone know where stupid zenk has
最后我听说他在和竖琴手和摩根一起工作 盾牌很棒
last i heard he was working with harpers and Morgan shield great
竖琴手
harpers
这是他与竖琴手的问题
it's his problem with harpers
好吧 我们走吧
all right let's go
打扰一下
excuse me
我还活着
i'm still alive
是的
right
你最喜欢的书是什么
what's your favorite book
如何只挑一个
how to pick just one
那是个问题
that's a question
什么
what
差不多
kinds of
历史作品我会说 likeanthasar 的方墓
historical works i'd say the Fang tomb of likeanthasar
那只是第四个问题
that was only the fourth question
你好
hello
让我们来看看
let's see
更有意思的
more interesting
Zank 是它
Zank is it
它不询问我提供了没有九个给谁的答案
it doesn't query i provide off to answer without nine to whom
我在说
i'm speaking
我是 Holga Kilbor
i'm Holga Kilbor
这是 Simon Edgin 和 Dorick Beck
this is Simon Edgin and Dorick Beck
是什么带来了它的晨盾
what brings its morning shield
你做
you do
我们正在努力寻找功能障碍的头盔
we're trying to find the helmet of dysfunction dysfunction
许多谎言都在捍卫那个掌舵人的过程中消失了
many lies are lost in defense of that helm
说一点减少他们的牺牲
to speak a bit of which diminish their sacrifice
简也为你飞驰好声音
Jan fleets for you as well a good sound
以诚实正直着称
known as a man of honor and integrity
我可以向你保证
and i can assure you
看头盔的原因完全是新星是的
are reasons for watching the helmet are entirely nova yep
它抢劫
it robs
霍加
hoga
啊不只是任何人堡垒威廉
ah not just anyone fortrefts William
在红胜天伙伴
in the red wins of days partner
跟我来
come with me
这是什么地方
what is this place
海港保护区
a harbor sanctuary
你的朋友 edpie 肯定已经知道了
surely your friend edpie already knew that
我确实知道作为一个竖琴手
i do know as a harper
你可能已经完全宣誓
you may have full sworn your oath
但你的誓言还没有完全宣誓
but your oath hasn't full sworn
这里
here
就因为那句话
just because that sentences
对称并不意味着它没有意义
a symmetrical doesn't make it not not sense
为什么你希望拉尔夫和他在一起
why do you wish to Ralph it's with him
他偷了
he stole
阿德金的女儿和我们的大量财宝
Adkin's daughter and a great deal of treasure from us also
一块重新觉醒的石板甚至不知道
a tablet of re awakening doesn't even know that
换句话说 Forge 是一个真正的狗娘养的
in other words forge is a real son of a bitch
所以你把他的腐败归咎于他的母亲
so you blame his mother for his corruption
什么
what
不 它是一个表达式
no it's an expression
我懂了
i see
我不知道交通和口语
i didn't know traffic and colloquialisms
你不是很有趣吗
you're not a lot of fun are you
如果是 William 真的与红巫师结盟
if it's William is truly allied with a red wizard
他们的意图必须超越奇迹
their intentions must go beyond the miracle is
当我们被派去护卫队时
when we were sent fairguard
zas Tam 的亡灵是八岁的孩子之一
the necromance of zas Tam is one of eight years old kids
谁统治了信仰之国
who ruled the nation of faith
伟大的
great
因为时间对力量的渴望绝对是
for time's hunger for power was absolutely
在日落前夕
on the Eve of the sunsets
胶囊的居民聚集在一起庆祝
the residents of the capsule gathered for a celebration
我快到那个程度了
i'm almost to that well
他的变量有他自己的计划
his variables to have a plan of his own
上演一场邪恶的酷
to stage an unholy cool
年轻的死亡国度
young nation of beckoning death
我们吞噬周围战争灵魂的雪
the snow that we consume the souls of war around it
睡觉直到它会
sleeping until it will
创造了他的红巫师 刚刚创造了亡灵大军
created his red wizards just have created the army of the undead
让他征服整个国家
allowing him to conquer the entire nation
南方的力量不超过仙女的边界
southern power stands no further than the borders of fay
我怀疑他和他的红巫师不会满足
i suspect he and his red wizards will not be content
直到他们实际上已经失败了
until they have in fact of the whole of failing
完成他们的恶作剧
with their malevisons done
因为我们已经知道红巫师很坏
because we already know that red wizards are bad
所以确实提出了问题
and so does forge the question
仍然是他们帮助并掌权了他们做了什么
remains that they helped and take power what do they
有收获
stand to gain
听起来我们有共同的敌人
sounds like we have a common enemy
你给了我们锻造下来的头盔
you give us that helmet we take forged down
如果有一笔财富来支持他们 就没有人会继续做主
no one stays lord if that a fortune to back them up
红巫师失去了他们的傀儡
and the red wizards lose their puppet
富有的窃贼会变成什么样子
what will become of the wealthy burgle
那有什么关系
what does that matter
我不会同谋使用 ilgotten 战利品
i will not be complicit in the elicited use of ilgotten booty
和
and
美好的
fine
分为
divided amongst
市民发誓
the townspeople swear to it
是的
right
将你的手放在这只无害的海豹上
place your hand on this harpless seal
并发誓你确实会分配所有的财富
and swear that you will indeed distribute all the wealth
你置身于从未有过冬天的人群中
you take amongst the people of never winter
没问题
sure fine
继续前进
go on head
承诺你会为只是一个人付出
promise you'll give for just one into people
承诺
promise on
给从不穿的人要塞钱
give fortress money to the people who never wear
拿着吧
keep this
你可能还不相信你的话 但我相信
you may not yet believe your words but i do
现在的夏山
summer mountains now
幽暗地域的瓶子里的头盔在哪里
where's the helmet in the bottles of the underdark
暗处
the underdark
你试图保证它的安全吗
were you trying to keep it safe
你为什么要把它放在那里
why would you put it down there
因为它只是任何珍惜生命的人的迷失之地
because it's just the lost place of anyone who values their life
会去听起来很可爱恰恰相反
would go sounds lovely quite the opposite
我知道我在讽刺
i i know i was being ironic
我发现讽刺就像一把几乎看不到谁在挥舞它的刀刃
i find irony as a blade that can't see who wield it almost
尤其是
especially yeah
这么多你很好沉
so much you fine sink
剑山东边有个入口
there is an entrance east of the sword mountains
在地穴花园森林里
in the crypt garden forest
从
from
我们可以下到都柏林的根
which we may descend to the roots of Dublin
这可能是如此大胆
that may be so bold
让你宣布选项
cause you to announce the options
我的心都碎了我的妻子被杀
my heart broke out my wife killed
对不起
i'm sorry
我要沉默我的正义吗
do i silence my justice
你说的粉丝
the fans you mean
粉丝不在水平线上
fans are not on the levelness
作为一个男孩 当时间看到控制时 他们会获胜
as a boy wins as time sees control as they
我看到了第一手的恐怖是咒语
i saw a first hand the horror is the spell
尊贵的人变成了混蛋
honorable man turn to bastards
头脑湿润干净 时刻
minds wet clean and moments
拉伦斯
larrence
转向自己的孩子
turning on their own child
我活着逃了
i escaped alive
但永远改变了
but forever changed
你我都失去了自己的一部分
you and i have both lost a part of ourselves
所有匹配的都是我们用剩下的东西做的
all that matches is what we do with much remains
我告诉过你我要做什么
i told you what i'm gonna do
我们正在打破演员表 我们永远无法让我的家人回来
we're breaking the cast we'll never get my family back
平板电脑计划复活一个妻子是的
the tablet planned to resurrect a wife yeah
很好
very well
不仅如此 您认为令人难以置信的酷生活
not only else that you consider the disclaiming cool life
是其中之一 嗯嗯
is one of many uh huh
把你的爱人拖回滚滚的生活
drag your lady love back to roll life
我的新人的幸存者可以在这个人旁边的其他人吗
surprivor of my new one can someone else right next to this guy
跟我来是办公室
follow me is the office
孔雀
the orifers
黑暗势力有很多兴趣
and the dark has many interests
这是最后一个引人注目的
this is one of the last conspicuous
今天的轨道
today's track
选择分开以避免民众保持亲密和安静
chosen apart to avoid the populace stay close and quiet
你听说过这个地方吗
that have you heard of this place
几乎是他真正危险的一小部分
nearly a fraction of his true danger
运送方式从礼物变成
ship the way becomes from gift
我可以牵着我的手 我会需要你
i may take my hand and i will need you
我现在就告诉你我要握住他的手
i'll tell you right now i'm gonna take his hand
关心他相信这个人
to be care about him trust this guy
你知道他在帮助我们
you know he's helping us
从袖子里拿点东西
to get something of the sleeve
我的袖子上有什么是我的手臂
there's anything on my sleeve is my arm
我能听到我也听到了
i can hear that i hear that as well
到废墟只有你
out to the ruins just you
摇摇晃晃地进入发誓要强大的吞噬者
rocking on into the devours sworn to formidable
他们击晕目标并消耗大脑
they stun their targets and consume the brain
控制身体
take control the body
你会怎样不发出声音
what would you make no sound
他们被精神能量所吸引
they're drawn to mental energy
猎物的智力越高
higher the intelligence of the prey
最近他们要罢工
more lately they are to strike
好吧 这有点伤人
well that's a little hurtful
有这个悬空的毒品之城
there is this hanging city of dope
头盔躺在这个鸿沟的快速生活上
the helmet lies on the fast life of this chasm
但警告说这座桥受到古老的诺姆斯陷阱的保护
but the warned the bridge is protected by an ancient nomus trap
他有一个精确的公式
there was a precise formula with his follows
尽可能多地触发机制
so as much trigger the mechanism
公式是什么
what's the formula
这很简单
it's quite simple
从中心开始使用奇数块
starting from the center used odd number blocks
除了每五步之外 只向前迈出每一步
only working forward with each step except for every fifth step
这必须是最后一个滚动运动
which must be a last roll movement
左还是右
left or right
没关系那么久
it matters not so long
作为落后者中的领导者在之后保持等距
as the leader in the lagged remain equidistant after
它继续
which it proceed
然而肯定又是奇数块
again odd number blocks certainly however
并且中点在偶数块中切换
and the midpoint was switched in even number blocks
同样的恐慌和横向运动
same panics and that lateral movement
前
before
我可能有
i may have
把我的脚放在桥上
put my foot on the bridge
并意识到那是我开始的地方
and realize that's where i take it started
所以
so
对不起
sorry
它在结构上不是很南
it's not very structurally south
你就不能用魔法让我们穿越吗
can't you just magic us across
唔
hmm
这太过分了
it's too far tuck case this
我包里有绳子
i've got some rope in my bag
我可以把它绑在斧头上
i could tie it to the axe
把它扔过去 让它粘在岩石上
toss it across so it sticks to the rock
你知道石头很硬就闭嘴
you know rocks are hard right shut up
你得到了什么
what did you get that
当我女人的手杖
when my woman's walking stick
我从一个巫师那里滑过葡萄
i swiped it from a wizard over the grapes
它不是手杖
it's not a walking stick
这是第五名员工
it's a hit the fifth staff
什么
what
应该在五点左右带着克拉等待
should have been waiting around five with karats
手表
watch
打
hit the
它是
it was
甚至不需要朋友
didn't even need the friends
我做得很好
i did good
正如我现在给你的
as i gave you now
信任形象会用你的生命保护它
trust image will protect it with your very life
我会
i will
为了这
for this
这里有邪恶
there is evil here
是那些
are those
幻想
fantasies
让我们去
let us go
下来市中心
come down downtown
这不是我们的戏剧
it's not our dramas
他们是 但他们是积极的 我是你的灵魂
they are but they are positives i am your soul
我不知道为什么
i don't know why
我很新鲜
i'm down fresh
带他们到我这里来
lead them to me
滑翔在我们这边
gliding's on our side
我们会睡觉
we will sleep
为什么你把他们都杀了
why you killed them all
没有简单的脚可以杀死已经死去的东西
there's no simple feet to kill that which is already dead
那是一只卫生龙它是丹佛短
that's one hygie dragon it's Denver short
那是新的死亡的声音
it was the sound of new death
他吃了最后一个吗
did he eat the last one
感谢那
thanks for that
你也为我做了同样的事
you've done the same for me
快点
come on
我有一个鼓
i got a drum
那是什么
what was that here
我只能拉到那个工具
i could only pull to that tool
我看得出你想从那堵墙走到那堵墙
i can see you wanna go from that wall to that wall
某处
somewhere
钻石记得那个棘手的然后干更新鲜的切割十字铃
diamond remember that tricky then dry more fresh cut crossbell
没有翻转片状图一凝胶一
no the flip flake figure one gel one
我们要打击他们想让它适合你
we're gonna hit them wanna make it fine for you
当我这么说的时候
when i say so
每个人都去水下 那将是你的七个
everybody goes underwater and that'll be your few seven
好的
all right
你在看什么
what are you looking at a harper
摆脱
shaking off
这东西
this stuff
回家等一下
go home hold up
这就是我离开你的原因
that's why i leave you
这是您在飞机上的每一次成功
it's your every success on your jet
你不来我能做的事
you not come what that i could
这是你的任务
this is your quest
我已经给了你必须使用的工具
i have given you the tools you must utilize them
你不能为我们利用它们吗
can't you utilize them for us
因为你好多了而且战斗和策略很漂亮
because you're much better and fighting and strategy pretty
除了我在说什么
much everything but i'm talking
谈音乐很棒
talk music great
在那些伴随着信仰浪潮的情况下 怀疑越来越多
in those instances with faith waves doubt waxes
我记得当时的租户还可以
i recall the tenants at the age it's okay
回头见
see you later
他去了
there he goes
只是徘徊
just wandering off
走在这样一条直线上
walks in such a straight line
哦 等一下 他正爬上一块石头 它会绕过去吗
oh wait a minute he's coming up on a rock is it gonna go around
没有
nope
马上就来
right over
我赶紧去欢呼我不能连接它是无用的
i'm hurry to a cheer i can't connect it to be useless
这是很大的压力 只有通过才能得到它
that's a lot of pressure giving only went through to get it
是的 我意识到
yeah i realized that
所以整个命运都在你身上
so entire fate rests on you
那里
there
他是伟大的西蒙正常
he is the great Simon normal
它也是我们伦敦巫师的后裔
it's also our descendant from wizarding in London
你是谁你不认识我吗
who are you don't you know me
我的名字是洛马托
my name is lomato
你是我的曾曾祖父
you're my great great grandfather
那真是个家
that's quite a home
是什么让你觉得
what makes you think
你配得上
you're worthy of it
我相信我自己 你问的是不 我确定
i believe in myself you're asking no i'm sure
我是一个休息的孩子
i'm a break children
哦 你知道
oh you know
关于魔术的有趣的事
funny thing about magic
它选择我的轮子得到谁并且它不会遭受傻瓜
it chooses who my wheel gets and it doesn't suffer fools
你为什么要告诉我这个
why are you telling me this
哦
oh
我想你知道
i think you know
你转身了吗
did you turn with it
好的
okay
一个人发生的事
what happened alone
我呃
i uh
我和我曾曾祖父那样的人说过话
i spoke to someone like that my great great grandfather
曾是
was
对你说话没有帮助
un helpful you spoke to
从这里看起来头盔飞走了
from here it looked like the helmet flew off
和你推迟一样
the same you put it off
好吧 这次以不同的方式向后移动
well this time moves differently back
好的
okay
我会尝试不同的方法
i'll try a different approach
伟大的新方法尝试
great new approach try
你明白了 你明白了
you got this you got
你越来越好了 生病了 你
you're getting better getting fives far sick with it you
需要六个小时才能离开永远的赢家
need six hours till we leave forever winner
你失败了 我再也没有让我的家人回到辉煌
you fail i never got my family back brilliant
我从未见过比他更懦弱的人
i've never seen a bigger coward
胆小鬼你也在这里
coward you're under here too
好吧 我会处理的 不 不
fine i'll handle it no no
我有这个
i've got this
和
and
那你想成为一个哈珀骚乱
then you wanna be a harper riot
所以我试图捕捉它
so i'm trying to capture it
只需要放手
just have to let it go
宠物
pet
宠物我们买了一个问题我做不到
pet we bought a problem i can't do it
该死的
damn it
啊 我已经搞了几个小时了 我抓到你这个老混蛋
ah i've been at it for hours i caught you passy old bastard
我说我无法实现现在我是废话
i said i couldn't achieve now i'm the crap
什么是球拍
what's the racket
他在寻求帮助时遇到了一些麻烦
he's having a little trouble with that help
来吧 西蒙 去做吧
come on Simon just do it
哦 是的 好的 是的
oh yeah okay yeah
谢谢霍加 我会做的
thanks hoga i'll just do it
这正是我告诉过你回到塔宾会发生的事情
this is exactly what i told you would happen back to the tabin
但你不会听
but you wouldn't listen
你告诉他什么意思
what do you mean you told him
他说为了鼓舞士气 我不知道为什么
he said to keep it between us for morale i didn't know why
因为他是我认识的最猪头的人
because he is the most pig headed person i've ever known
你说服我们做你知道行不通的事情
you talk us into doing things you know won't work
然后当它变得耐心时你会责怪我们如果你能调
and then you blame us when it goes patient if you can a tune
我们会想出一个计划b
we'll figure out a plan b
计划b
plan b
我们挖出了我的家人 我们去地底暗区拿了那个头盔
we dug up my family we went to the underdark for that helmet
你一直都知道他无法使用它
and you knew the whole time that he couldn't use it
你们人类就是忍不住撒谎
you humans you just can't help but lie
我没有撒谎 我真的认为西蒙可以做男人的样子
i didn't lie i really thought Simon could do guys look
我们还有几个小时的比赛时间
we got a couple hours still the games
忘记这就是我们所做的
forget this is what we do
我们转向而不是纠结于哪里出了问题
we pivot instead of dwelling on what went wrong
谁对谁撒谎 让我们集思广益
who lied to whom let's put our heads together and figure out a
计划我会找到回家的路
plan i'm gonna figure out my way home
我不敢相信我相信你们中的任何一个是的
i can't believe i put my faith in any of you yeah
我会为基拉感到抱歉
i'm going to sorry about Kira
找到另一种方法来得到她只是不是今天
find another way to get her just not today
必须是今天 直到我女儿安全 我们才结束
has to be today we're not done until my daughter's safe
你不厌倦失败吗？
don't you sick of failing no
这就是我们绝不能停止失败的重点
that's the whole point we must never stop failing
因为我们做的那一刻
because the minute we do
我们失败了
we failed
看我们这里没有人能说出我们的生活
look none of us here can say our lives
已经走了我们希望的路
have gone the way we had hoped for
是的
right
霍尔加你离开了你的部落去和一个离开你的人在一起
holga you left your tribe to be with a man who left you
因为你对离开你的部落感到非常沮丧
because you were so upset about leaving your tribe
如果你现在退出
and if you quit now
那是石头
that's in stone
和你签的一样
same with you signed it
你是一个小偷大盗 作为一个小资源提供者
you're a petty thief mass grating as a petty resourcer
你得回你的店
you gotta go back to your shop
最好是垂死的
is best the dying
有比死去的笨蛋更糟糕的事情
there's worse things than dying dork
你有诚信
you have integrity
我确定你最不想做的事
and i am sure the last thing you want to do
是告诉翡翠飞地你有机会救他
is tell the emerald enclave that you had a chance to save him
但你走开了嘿
but you walked away hey
你很快就说我们失败了你和我呢
you're quick to call us failures what about you and me
我是失败的冠军
i'm the champion of failures
我失去了对我来说最重要的一切
i lost everything that ever mattered to me
都是我的错
and it was all my fault
我真的会杀了我的妻子吗
would i really killed my wife
我做了
i did
我决定
i decided
我们应该过比房子里的哈珀区更好的生活
we deserved better life than a harper zone through our house
但我不知道红巫师标记了他们的宝藏
but i didn't know that red wizards marked their treasure
让他们到我们家门口
let them right to our door
当他们到达那里时 我什至没有好运回家
i didn't even have a good luck to be home when they got there
辜负了竖琴手 我辜负了我的家人 我辜负了你们所有人
failed the harpers i failed my family i failed all of you
这正是我不能退出的原因所以如果你能原谅我
which is exactly why i can't quit so if you'll excuse me
我要去坐在这块石头上
i'm gonna go sit on this rock
制定一个计划
make a plan
它是做什么的 但是没有
what's it do but there's no
更多的
more
对这个
about this
我们使用他们的员工进入保险库
we use the hither that their staff to get into the vault
我已经解释过你不能把它打到房间里因为
i've explained that you can't hit the thither into a room cause
我不是说我是说
i'm not saying that i'm saying
我们把传送门放在某物上
we put the portal on something
然后把那东西偷偷带进金库
and then sneak that thing into the vault
进入那个金库的唯一东西就是宝藏
the only thing going in that vault is treasure
所以我们把传送门放在一些宝藏上
so we put the portal on some treasure
因为你说的是??巴尔塔最富有的人给了他们
for what you did say the richest men in baltars gave them
水更深 给城市带来战利品
water deeper bringing loot to the city
我会沿着高速公路行驶 我们可以赶上他们的一个
i'll be traveling the high road we can catch one of their
车队但是有几十个警卫是的
convoys but there be dozens of guards yeah
警卫会提防
the guards would be guarding against
人们把东西从他们的马车里拿出来而不是把它们放进去
people taking things out of their wagon without putting them in
哦上帝可以吻你
oh god could kiss you
多么深刻的
what a profound
喜悦
joy
这是你好你的好
it is to welcome you the good
人从来没有时间复工
people have never been time to the resumption
我们的眼睛在这里
of our eyes are here
我保证
i guarantee
你来这里是为了最聪明的奇观
that you are here for the most intelligent spectacle of
受你好的突击海岸
popular assault coast
威尼斯人的规则
the rules of venicipal
五个着色挑战
five coloring challenges
五支冠军队伍
five teams of champions
谁活到焦虑笼避难所
whoever survives to anxiety cage sanctuary
进入下一阶段
moves on for the next stage
我中的一个人我确实在争论
one of me i do argue
请不要离开竞技场
please do not leave the arena
到大门的尽头 因为会有我们自己的
to the close of the gate as there will be our own
每个人的礼物
gift for each and every one
这是荒谬的高 不会被讨论
this is absurdly high it's not gonna be discussed
不好了
oh no
发生了什么
what happened
它面对着四个
it's facing the four
为什么要这样存放
why were they stored that way
为什么什么都不如我们所愿
why does nothing go our way
让我试试 也许我可以挑选帽子
let me try maybe i can pick the cap
比赛开始
games started
我们要种植c
we're going to plant c
哦 胡说八道 什么是 plant c
oh bollocks what's plant c
计划c
plan c
我们回去计划
is we go back to plan a
你会适应头盔
you're gonna attune to the helmet
为什么你不直接称它为行星
why Don't you just call it planet
飞机上有水槽
plane has a sink on it
你他妈的很清楚我无法适应那些不真实的事情
you know damn well i can't attune to the things that's not true
你无法适应它
you couldn't attune to it
看着我
look at me
看着我 啊 你把那份工作大声水
look at me ah you run that job aloud water
你不能蜘蛛爬
you couldn't spider climb
直到约翰逊把他的狗粘在你身上
until Johnson sticked his dog on you
当我们夺取誓言的长矛时
and when we rob the spear of a oath fezzing
你的石皮法术失败了 直到箭离你几英寸远
your stone skin spell failed until the arrows were inches away
即使在三胞胎
even in triborn
你翻转了整个剧院的引力
you flip the gravity of a whole theater
你做了
you did
偶然的 这是疯狂的魔法 而且只是发生了
by accident it was wild magic and that only happened
因为他们要
because they were gonna
准确地杀了我
kill me exactly
看
look
当你认为自己最弱的时候 你才是最强的
you are at your strongest when you think you're at your weakest
但你交付
but you deliver
你会进入那个金库好吧
you're gonna get into that vault okay
因为你不能
because you can't
但因为你必须
but because you must
我会继续绊倒
i'm gonna keep tripping away
如果我能得到四分之一
if i can get a quarter
英寸你将能够像蠕虫一样挤过
inch you'll be able to squeeze through as a worm
有一条虫
there's a worm
呃 有虫子
uh there's a worm
完美 你现在看到了 我们有计划 c 的计划 d 失败了
perfect you see this now we have a plan d of plan c fails
不是计划 d 只是再次计划 d
isn't plan d just plan d again
哦 计划 d 也是一根棍子 它都粘在这里
oh plan d is a stick too it all sticks here
用它来保持联系
use this to keep in contact
嗯 这是一块石头
well um this is a rock
实际上它是一个发送区
actually it is a sending zone
但目前只有一个
but the only one for now
那我们怎么进去
so how are we gonna get in there
很简单 我们只是制造了一种干扰
easy we just create a distraction
嗯 我对植物有很好的感觉
well i got a good feeling about plants
你在这里做什么
what's your business here
战斗结束朋友成为恋人儿子拥抱母亲
the battle is over friends become lovers sons embrace mothers
兄弟和爸爸
brothers and dads
曾经竞争的地方
where once were contend
庆祝眼镜
celebrate glasses
我想他们开始怀疑了
i think they're starting to get suspicious
治疗水果在那里找到我们会遇到的金库
cure fruits be up there find the vault we'll meet
好吧 你可以这样做放松和迷恋
okay you can do this relax and crush
他在那
there he is
谁回去
who goes back
那太街头了 我没有时间做这个
that would be so street i don't have time for this
一直有你不在乎我们会死
all the time there is you Don't care that we're going to die
如果我不恨你
if i Don't hate you
所以你死得像??个傻瓜
so you die a fool
这比让我们活得足够好
it's better than to live us one that's enough
你不认识我我知道
you Don't know me i know
你是你家族名誉上的污点 让我的名字见鬼去吧
you're a stain on your family name to hell with my name
让我一个二
let me a two
不是我的生活你不要生活你有你的时间
not what i live you Don't live you had your time
现在轮到我了
now it's my turn
我不在乎
i don't care
对不起
sorry
花了足够长的时间
took a long enough
是我做得很好
it was i did it well done
是的 只是我阻止了我 就是这样
yes it was just me holding me back that's what
我疯了
i'm insane
使它在故障内
made it inside the fault
我们也是
so did we
这里什么都没有
there's nothing here
也许一切都在这里你在哪里
maybe it's all here where are you
你在哪
where are you
我们来到竞技场下
we come under the arena
锻造
forge
西蒙·约克你在
Simon York you there
你在这里做什么
what are you doing here
这里
here
我是来找你的 我们得走了
i came for you we have to go
他喜欢成为
he loves to be
不 不
no no
我知道你认为我是个骗子和坏父亲但是
i know you think i'm a liar and a bad father but
我是个坏爸爸
i am a bad father
我确实离开了你
and i did leave you
我不是想把你妈妈带回来我只是想
and i wasn't trying to bring your mom back i was just trying to
把我的妻子带回来
bring my wife back
如果可能有几种机会
which if maybe a few kinds of chances that are
恋爱或喜欢
in love or like
我是你不明白但如果你现在跟我来
i did you don't understand but if you come with me now
你可以有那个机会
you can have that chance
你认为你会
you think you'd be
能够区分自己的
able to distinguish between your own
门和一个三百年的巫师
doors and a three hundred year old wizard
有一个奇怪的保险箱
there are a curious safe
我喜欢使命
i'm like mission
不知道你要来
no idea you were coming
我不认为她知道你变得多么顽强
i don't think she knows how tenacious you've become
对于事情的结果我真的很抱歉
i'm really sorry about the way things worked out
但我认为如果你真的诚实
but i think if you were truly honest
你不得不承认我可以给基拉更好的生活
you'd have to admit i can give Kira a better life
我希望你知道后能感到安慰
i hope you can take comfort in knowing that
她和她应得的父亲在一起
she's with the father she deserves
现在我很困惑 因为
now i'm in a pickle because
我不想看到你死
i Don't want to see you die
这就是为什么
which is why
我会听到屋顶的声音
i'm gonna hear the roof
如果你要杀了我们至少让我们从尊严开始
if you're gonna kill us at least let us start with dignity
你是什??么意思让我们参加烈日游戏
how do you mean put us in the high sun games
给我们一个战斗的机会
give us a fighting chance
那不是机会
that's not a chance
这根本不是机会
it's not a chance at all
即使你能活下来 我也告诉他关于 safenas 的事
even if you were to survive i told him about safenas
护士
nurse
对你来说会好得多
it would be much much better for you to
你在这里去参加比赛不
thy here and go to the games no
他们打败了你我的人 让他们在竞技场上战斗
they defeated your men and mine let them fight in the arena
他们应得的
they deserve that much
我回去睡觉的路
my way back to sleep
我们是
are we
竞技场
the arena
这个假人说要让我们参加比赛假人
this dummy talked forward into putting us in the games dummy
我救了我们的命
i saved our lives
我把我们带到了宝藏戈登所在的正上方
and i got us right above where gordons at the treasure was
是不是有点怀疑
is it a little suspect
那就是如果你知道什么同意这个
that's if you know what agree to this
是的 她肯定是有计划的
yeah she's definitely planned something
没有一个 Irale 战士
none of the Irale warrior
你是否记得
do you remember
没有把握
not sure
下面有一个码头
there's a dock down there
我看到守卫把所有东西都装上船
i saw guards loading everything onto a ship
一艘船
a ship
Forge 躲着我们
forge was hiding from us
他在为自己偷走他
he was stealing him for himself you never care about being lord
那只是给了金库最大值
that just gave maxes to the vault
如果磁带更大 他会带回游戏
he was a brought back the game should the tape would be bigger
关于基罗
about kiro
我们会没事的 我们必须去那艘船
we'll be fine we have to get to that boat
我不明白索菲亚是否只是离开了什么
i don't understand if for just leaving what does Sophia get out
这个的
of this
出色地
well
我可以带我们离开这里
i can get us out of here
魔法压制袖套
magic suppression cuff
他们给我小费
they put one on me tip
真的很擅长
just really good at
我们只是穿过迷宫
we just go through the maze
我想我们达到了改变
i guess we reach the change
你试过我这个地方吗
have you tried this place based me
不 这太游戏了
no it's too games
看来我的船已经准备好悲伤
it seems my ship is ready sorrow
小心 我会在下面
care and i will be taking underneath
我希望我们的合作
i do hope that our collaboration
很高兴离开我的城市
is gratified to get out of my city
一分钟之内我就会失去我的手
in a minute i would have lost my hand
是的 你确实输了
yeah well you did lose
现在这是向上的路
now this is the way up
这就是如果我们活下来
this is this if we survive this
他将是另一个挑战 直到
he'll be another challenge and another until
那个笼子里的最后一个人都死了
every last person in that cage is dead
我们得四处看看
we have to find a look around
我有一个想法跟我来
i've got an idea follow me
你想像那个人一样结束
you want to end up like that guy
在里面滚动几秒钟
rolling inside for a few seconds
在里面他会把我们拉出来我会永远相信我
all inside he's gonna pull us out i will trust me always
你有那种状态吗
do you have with that state
我来过这里
i've been here
在这里工作
work here
俱乐部的十块土地
ten land in the club
跟我来
come with me
相当不错的第二次约会吧
quite a second date huh
旅行是的
a trip yes
有紧急事情发生 如果我们现在可以离开
something urgent has come up and if we can leave now
我们会很安全的
we'll be safe safe for what
这是什么这是伏击
what is this this is an ambush
在船上 我们将用来逃避我们所做的一切
on the boat and we're gonna use to escape from whatever we do
嗨亲爱的嘿锻造你为什么不告诉她这是什么
hi honey hey forge why don't you tell her what this is
我不知道
i Don't know
它是
it's the
在基拉自由醒来的平板电脑这是我离开你的原因
tablet of free waking in Kira it's the reason why i left you
你爸爸一直在告诉你真实地点
your dad's been telling you the true spot
一直在找草料的叔叔
the uncle forage who's been fiending
Elias 哈哈哈 垃圾 跟我来 Kiru
Elias Hahaha rubbish that's just rubbish come with me Kiru
回家带妈妈回来
go home bring back mom
我们可以再次成为一家人
we can be a family again
你没有拿我的钱
you're not taking my money
放下平板电脑 现在你们所有人都离开我的船
put down the tablet and get off my ship all of you now
好的
okay
你在干什么
what are you doing
对不起搜索我亲爱的安静它正在下降
sorry search my darling quiet it's going down
看到基拉
see that Kira
跟随那些
follow those
他知道我准备做可怕的事情来得到我想要的
he knows i'm prepared to do terrible things to get what i want
甚至对那些
even to those
我最关心
i care about most
在头脑中 这就是它分开的一切
in the head that's all it separates
在这里这是我的错误
over here it's my bug
谁知道灰手上有两万
who knows twenty thousand on the gray hands
对不起 我相信
i'm sorry i believe that
你在说什么 什么都没有
what are you talking about nothing
你没有什么道歉
you've nothing apologize
我应该为此感到抱歉
i should sorry that
我道歉
i apologize
我爱你
i love you
没有什么会再次摆脱
there nothing will ever get away from again
它一直很可爱
it's been having that cute
你去
there you go
有多少新闻
how much news is on
这艘船哈哈惊喜漂浮之书
this ship haha surprise the book of float
好吧 它是如此的爱针
alright it's so needle in love
那是什么
what is that
这是小路的后面
this is the back of the path
因此
that's why
她确实伪造了
she did forge
奥运会让这座城市团结起来
the games brought the city together forth spell
大小城镇正在外卖
size town is taking out
好该死的
well shit
继续努力 西蒙 你说什么
work it on and Simon what did you say
范围是那种门户风格
the range was of that portal style
为了微笑什么
for smile what
uppermaster hustle 你在吗
uppermaster hustle are you here
作为永冬之王
as lord of never winter
我吞噬了这艘船并巡航追逐了五个人但是
i devour the ship and cruise chase down five people but
打击犯罪
fight crimes
谢谢你喜欢
thanks for you enjoy that
好的
all right
在我们带她出去之前这还没有结束
this isn't over till we take her out
无论我们发生什么
whatever happens to us
留在
stay in
谁悔改了
who's repented
我们要做什么才能做到这一点我明白了
what are we doing to get to i got this
这是另一次停止兴奋柜台是
it's another time stop excited the counter is
我的天还是太螺丝了
my god is still too screws
我很抱歉
i'm so sorry
时间过长
for too long
我忍受了阿拉伯语 维托利亚堡 虚假的魅力
i endured the arabics the fort vittolia the false charm
毛骨悚然 就在我开始的时候
the creeps and just as i begin
清除这个地方的生活污秽 你胆敢变成骨头
to purge this place of its living filth you dare into bones
现在你死了
now as you die
以表明这不会是结束
as to show it will not be the end
你将永远受苦
you will forever suffer
啊
ah
对不起 你的兄弟听起来像
sorry your brother just sounds like
拿衣服不好
hold clothes it's bad
这是什么
what is this
计入你的时间停止
accounted your time stop
比赛
the competition
有了你应该关心的轨道 你可以睡在袖口
with the track you should care you can slept by the cuff
它应该工作
and it should work
做这个
do this
我想你得到了她
i think you got her
我不认为那个计划已经结束
i don't think that plan was gone
你向我们保证它会
you assured us it would
嘿霍加
hey hoga
我们找到她了吗天啊
did we get her oh god
是的
yeah
是的 我们得到了她
yeah we got her
哦那不是一个好地方是不是
oh that's that's not a good spot is it no
它不是
it's not
这还不错
it's not bad
这里
here
西蒙西蒙帮她
Simon Simon help her
它是一块有显示的岩石
it's a rock with displayed
我无能为力
there's nothing i can do
你好
hi
我们会让你出局 那不会是个傻瓜
we're gonna pass you out that's not gonna be a fool
请不要走
please don't go
请不要轻易
please don't go easy
不要我
don't want me
不不不不不不不最后的话没有最后的话
no no no no no no no final words no final words
我为我在这里所做的感到自豪
i'm proud of what i did here
垂死的英雄
dying hero
到新
to new
你是一个好人
you're a good man
真正的港湾
a real harbor
闭嘴你知道的白痴
shut up a moron you know
那
that
答应我一件事
promise me something
甚至照顾我们的女孩
even to take good care of our girl
她是你做过的最棒的事
she's the best thing you ever did
我会
i will
没有财富淹没
no fortune drown
没有假神靠近东京自然滑线
no fake divine go close to Tokyo naturally slither line
你
you
残忍你说不坚定
cruel you said unsway
不
no
我需要你
i need you
闪亮的镜头
shining shots
我的生活
my life
他们不会杀了我吗
won't they kill me
是时候我们对此感到高兴了
that's time we'll be happy about this
好吧 如果他来找我们 我们就等着
well if he comes after us we'll be right wait
哦 是的 你不喜欢太多交易
oh that's right you don't like too much deal
某处好
somewhere okay
你呢
what about you
回到竖琴手那里
go back to the harpers
与人民同在
be with the people
我和我的人在一起
i'm with my people
所以
so
我知道我最后一次注意到你在家里很糟糕
i know my last attention caught you was quite bad at home
但我想知道你是否会考虑再去一次
but i wonder if you'd consider having another go to
是的 好吧 是的 公司
yeah all right yeah company
是的
right
该死的嫉妒
bloody jealous
你当然知道
of course you know
受够了 Savino 的魔法被抹去 Lord never ever
enough after that with Savino's magic expunged Lord never ever
最后凯奇
finally Cage
他的第一个官方行为是奖励操作员的救星
his first official act was to award the saviors of an operator
来自 Hellison 勋章
from medal of Hellison
和酋长国飞地
and to the emirate enclave
他正式保护他们人民的生命
he granted formal protection of their people of their life
没有人会争辩说我的行为应该受到谴责
no one could argue that my actions reprehensible
尽管他们引领了这座城市的虚拟复兴
though they were led to a virtual renaissance for the city
虽然我只服完刑期的第一年
and while i've only served the first year of my sentence i have
说它已经
to say it has been
我打开
i open
我已经采取
i have taken
看看里面
a look inside
我问过自己
and i've asked myself
那里发生了什么
what's going on in there
你知道我意识到
and you know i realized
很多都归功于我妈妈
a lot of it goes back to my mom
她是一个严厉的女人 事实证明视力会停止
she was a stern woman proved vision stop
停止我们听到另一个
stop we've heard another
手掌被拒绝
palm denied
会议是个笑话
the session is a joke